<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LeafPDF</string>
    <string name="tagline">Your Smart PDF Utility</string>
    <string name="privacy_title">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_text">PRIVACY POLICY — LeafPDF\n\nEffective Date: January 1, 2025\n\nLeafPDF ("we", "our", or "the app") is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how we handle information when you use our application.\n\n1. INFORMATION WE COLLECT\nLeafPDF does not collect or transmit any personal data to external servers. All PDF files, reading history, and preferences are stored locally on your device only.\n\n2. STORAGE ACCESS\nWe request storage permission solely to scan for and open PDF files on your device. We do not upload, share, or transmit your files to any server.\n\n3. ADVERTISING\nLeafPDF may display advertisements powered by Google AdMob. AdMob may collect device information for personalized ads. You can opt out of personalized ads in your device settings.\n\n4. ANALYTICS\nWe may use anonymized, aggregate usage analytics to improve the app. No personally identifiable information is collected.\n\n5. THIRD-PARTY LIBRARIES\nWe use open-source libraries for PDF rendering and image processing. These libraries do not collect user data.\n\n6. DATA SECURITY\nAll your data remains on your device. We implement security measures to protect locally stored data.\n\n7. CHILDREN\'S PRIVACY\nLeafPDF is not intended for children under 13. We do not knowingly collect data from children.\n\n8. CHANGES TO THIS POLICY\nWe may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Continued use of the app constitutes acceptance of the updated policy.\n\n9. CONTACT US\nIf you have questions, contact us at: support@leafpdf.app\n\nBy tapping "Allow", you agree to this Privacy Policy and grant the necessary permissions for the app to function.\n\nScroll to the bottom to enable the buttons.</string>
    <string name="btn_allow">✅ Allow &amp; Continue</string>
    <string name="btn_deny">❌ Deny &amp; Exit</string>
    <string name="scroll_hint">↓ Scroll to read the full policy</string>
    <string name="page_indicator">%1$d / %2$d</string>
    <string name="no_pdfs">No PDF files found.\nTap + to open a PDF.</string>
    <string name="loading_pdf">Loading PDF…</string>
    <string name="error_loading">Failed to load PDF</string>
</resources>
